Mss.B.W564
American Philosophical Society
- VI. Works by Others, 1926-1987 (Volume 90-110, Box 83-128)
  - Spontaneous Symmetry Breaking and Bifurcations from the Maclaurin and Jacobi Sequences, 1977; Michel, L., (Louis), 1923-; Constantinescu, Dan H.; Radicati, L. A. (Luigi Arialdo), 1919- (Box 107)
  - Analysis of Δ 1232 Polarization, 1978; Michel, L., (Louis), 1923-; Garcia Doncel, Manuel; Minnaert, Pierre (Box 107)
  - Spontaneous Breaking of Euclidean Invariance and Classification of Topologically Stable Defects and Configurations of Crystals and Crystals and Liquid Crystals, 1977; Michel, L., (Louis), 1923-; Kleman, Maurice (Box 107)
  - Application of Morse Theory to the Symmetry Breaking in the Landau Theory of Second Order Phase Transition, 1977; Michel, L., (Louis), 1923-; Mozrzymas, J. (Box 107)
  - Conformal Changes of Metrics in General Relativity, [1975]; Mielke, Eckehard W. (Box 107)
  - On Pseudoparticle Solutions in the Poincare Gauge Theory of Gravity, 1984; Mielke, Eckehard W. (Box 107)
  - Outline of a New Geometrodynamical Model of Extended Baryons, [1978]; Mielke, Eckehard W. (Box 107)
  - Positive Gravitational Energy in U 4 Theory, 1975; Mielke, Eckehard W. (Box 107)
  - Quatenfeldtheorie im de Sitter-Raum, 1976; Mielke, Eckehard W. (Box 108)
  - Very Massive Neutron Stars in NI's Theory of Gravity, [1977]; Mikkelsen, D. R. (Box 108)
  - Constraints on the Gravitational Constant at Large Distances, 1976; Mikkelsen, D. R.; Newman, Michael J. (Box 108)
  - Study of Henri Poincare's Sur la Dynamique de l'Electron, [1973]; Miller, Arthur I. (Box 108)
  - Foundations of Null-Strut Geometrodynamics, 1986; 2.0 folders; Miller, Warner Allen (Box 108)
  - Geometrodynamic Content of the Regge Equations as Illuminated by the Boundary of a Boundary Principle, 1985; Miller, Warner Allen (Box 108)
  - Quantum Insights from Null-Strut Geometrodynamics, 1987; Miller, Warner Allen; Kheyfets, Arkady; LaFave, Norman J. (Norman Joseph), 1958- (Box 108)
  - Observation of the Positronium Negative Ion, 1980; Mills, Allen P. (Box 108)
    Originally enclosed in Series IV: "Electron Pair Theory: Unfinished Tower"
  - Gauge Fields and the Gravity, Minkevich, A. V. (Box 108)
  - Gauge Fields and the Lorentz Group, 1974; Minkevich, A. V.; Kudin, V. I. (Box 108)
  - Closed Universe in Which There is a Uniform Electric Field with No Sources, 1954; Misner, Charles W. (Box 108)
  - Interpretation of Gravitational Wave Observations, 1972; Misner, Charles W. (Box 108)
  - On the Existence of Wormhole Solutions of the Einstein-Maxwell Equations, 1956; Misner, Charles W. (Box 108)
  - Spacetime Physics, [1960]; Misner, Charles W. (Box OS1)
    Galley proof. Oversized
  - Symmetry Paradoxes and Other Cosmological Comments, [1979]; Misner, Charles W. (Box 108)
  - Gravitational Synchrotron Radiation, 1971; Misner, Charles W. et al (Box 108)
  - Geometrical Gauge Theory of Gravity and Elementary Particle Forces, 1977; Moffat, John W. (Box 108)
  - Maximal Extension of a Non-Singular Solution in a Generalized Theory of Gravitation, 1977; Moffat, John W.; Kunstatter, G., (Gabor) (Box 108)
  - On the Physical Picture Underlying a Given Space-Time Solution. Gravitational Contraction, 1972; Møller, C., (Christian), 1904-1981 (Box 108)
  - Niels Bohr, [1962]; Møller, C., (Christian), 1904-1981; Pedersen, Johs.; Rosenfeld, L., (Leon), 1904-1974 (Box 108)
  - Coherent States and Quantum Non-Perturbing Measurements, 1977; Moncrief, Vincent (Box 108)
  - Gauge Symmetries of Yang-Mills Fields, 1976; Moncrief, Vincent (Box 108)
  - Hamiltonian Formalism for Relativistic Perfect Fluids, [1977]; Moncrief, Vincent (Box 108)
  - On the Vienna School of Statistical Thought, [1984]; Montroll, E. W., (Elliott W.) (Box 108)
  - ATP Hydrolysis Provides Energy in the Form of Entropy or Energy Transduction is Driven by an Entropy Change, 1985; Moore, Richard D. (Box 108)
  - K Factor: Reversing and Preventing High Blood Pressure Without Drugs. Chapter 19. How Science Works: Scientific Paradigm and Scientific Proof, 1985; Moore, Richard D. (Box 108)
  - Physical Definition of Meaning, 1975; Moore, Richard D. (Box 108)
  - Nuclear Code, [1985]; Morley, Peter D. (Box 109)
  - Time's Arrow and External Perturbations, 1963; Morrison, Philip (Box 109)
  - Stability and Nonlinear Character of Ordinary Differential Equations, 1962; Moser, Jurgen, 1928- (Box 109)
  - Cosmological Gulf between China and the Rest of the World, [1967]; Mote, Frederick W., 1922-2005 (Box 109)
  - [Abstract], n.d.; Moussouris, John P. (Box 109)
  - Applications of the DeSitter Group in Quantum Mechanics--Draft, 1982; 2.0 folders; Moylan, Patrick Joseph (Box 109)
  - Applications of the DeSitter Group in Quantum Mechanics--Manuscript, 1982; 2.0 folders; Moylan, Patrick Joseph (Box 109)
  - Intramolecular Rearrangement of Six-Coordinate Structures, 1968; Muetterties, Earl L. (Box 109)
  - Esquisse d'une Representation Generale et Formalisee des Descriptions et le Statut Descriptionnel de la Mecanique Quantique, 1984; Mugur-Schachter, Mioara (Box 109)
  - Creation Mechanized: The Crisis in the Arts and Literature, 1975; Murat, B. F. (Box 109)
  - Fulfillment of a Heritage, 1975; Murat, B. F. (Box 109)
  - Quantum Mechanics of Macroscopic Systems and the Measurement Process, [1986]; Namiki, Mikio (Box 109)
  - Tetrahydrobiopterin Administration for Parkinsonian Symptoms, [1982]; Narabayashi, Hirotaro, 1922- et al (Box 109)
  - Angular Appearance of White Holes, [1977]; Narlikar, Jayant Vishnu, 1938- (Box 109)
  - Anomalous Redshifts and Conformal Gravity, 1977; Narlikar, Jayant Vishnu, 1938- (Box 109)
  - Quantum Fluctuations in Gravitational Collapse and Cosmology, 1977; Narlikar, Jayant Vishnu, 1938- (Box 109)
  - Quantum Uncertainty in the Final State of Gravitational Collapse, 1977; Narlikar, Jayant Vishnu, 1938- (Box 109)
  - Space-Time and Physics in Terms of Particle Interactions, [1978]; Narlikar, Jayant Vishnu, 1938- (Box 109)
  - Determination of Properties of Cold Stars in General Relativity by a Variational Method, 1972; Nauenberg, Michael; Chapline, George (Box 109)
  - Clocks in Fields, n.d.; Neacsu, Alexander (Box 109)
  - Extended Event-Manifold, 1981; Neacsu, Alexander (Box 109)
  - Genesis and the Laws of Form, 1982; Neacsu, Alexander (Box 109)
  - Internal Time and the Delayed Choice Experiment, Neacsu, Alexander (Box 109)
  - Is the Black Hole the Final State?, 1982; Neacsu, Alexander (Box 109)
  - Space-Time Stability, 1982; Neacsu, Alexander (Box 109)
  - Time, 1981; Neacsu, Alexander (Box 109)
  - Gauged and Affine Quantum Gravity, 1979; Ne'eman, Yuval (Box 110)
  - Patterns, Structure, and then Dynamics: Discovering Unitary Symmetry and Conceiving Quarks, 1981; Ne'eman, Yuval (Box 110)
  - Problems in Quantum Foundations in the Light of Gauge Theories, 1985; Ne'eman, Yuval (Box 110)
  - Proposed Geometrizations for Unitary-Imposing Superalgebras of the Field/Ghost Systems, 1983; Ne'eman, Yuval (Box 110)
  - Spinor-Type Fields with Linear, Affine, and General Coordinate Transformations, 1977; Ne'eman, Yuval (Box 110)
  - Strings: From Hadron Dual Model to Gravity, Unification, and the Structure of Space-Time, 1986; Ne'eman, Yuval (Box 110)
  - Strings Reinterpreted as Topological Elements of Space Time, 1986; Ne'eman, Yuval (Box 110)
  - Supermanifolds and Berezin's New Integral, 1983; Ne'eman, Yuval (Box 110)
  - Ghost-Fields, BRS, and Extended Supergravity as Applications of Gauge Geometry, 1978; Ne'eman, Yuval; Regge, Tullio; Thierry-Mieg, J. (Box 110)
  - Algebra and Physics of the Unitary Multiplicity Free Representations of SL (4,R), 1985; Ne'eman, Yuval; Sijacki, Djordje (Box 110)
  - SL (4,R) World Spinors and Gravity, 1985; Ne'eman, Yuval; Sijacki, Djordje (Box 110)
  - Spinors for Superstrings in a Generic Curved Space, 1986; Ne'eman, Yuval; Sijacki, Djordje (Box 110)
  - Superstrings in a Generic Supersymmetric Curved Space, 1986; Ne'eman, Yuval; Sijacki, Djordje (Box 110)
  - Symmetry, Landau Theory, and Polytope Models of Glass, [1984]; Nelson, David R., 1951-; Widom, Michael (Box 110)
  - Paradox in the Exact Gravitational Plane Wave, 1980; Nelson, George (Box 110)
  - Chaotic Dynamics of Information Processing with Relevance to Cognitive Brain Functions, 1984; Nicolis,, J., (John), 1934- (Box 110)
  - Combinatorial Hierarchy -- An Approach to Open Evolution, 1980; Noyes, H. Pierre (Box 110)
  - Eternal Triangle Effect, 1979; Noyes, H. Pierre (Box 110)
  - Fixed Past and Uncertain Future: A Single-Time Covariant Quantum Particle Mechanics, Noyes, H. Pierre (Box 110)
  - Lowest Level of the Combinatorial Hierarchy as Particle Antiparticle Quantum Bootstrap, 1979; Noyes, H. Pierre (Box 110)
  - Terrestrial Revolution, n.d.; Noyes, H. Pierre (Box 110)
  - Philosophical Explorations. Chapter 3. Why is There Something Rather than Nothing?, [1980]; Nozick, Robert (Box 110)
  - Migration of Scientists from Latin America: Causes and Possible Solutions, [1969]; Nussenzveig, H. M., (Herch Moyses) (Box 110)
  - Theory of the Rainbow, n.d.; Nussenzveig, H. M., (Herch Moyses); Khare, V. (Box 110)
  - Geometry of Dynamics in General Relativity, [1972]; Nutku, Yavuz (Box 110)
  - Colliding Impulsive Gravitational Waves with Two Polarizations, [1977]; Nutku, Yavuz; Halil, M. (Mustafa) (Box 110)
  - Colliding Plane Gravitational Waves with Two Polarizations, [1977]; Nutku, Yavuz; Halil, M. (Mustafa) (Box 110)
  - Pion Elastic and Inelastic Scattering Near N=28 -- Draft, 1986; Oakley, David S. (Box 110)
  - Pion Elastic and Inelastic Scattering Near N=28 -- Manuscript, 1987; 2.0 folders; Oakley, David S. (Box 110)
  - On Birkhoff's Theory of Gravitation, 1975; Obregon, Octavio; Graef Fernandez, Carlos, 1911-1988 (Box 111)
  - Linearization Stability of Asymptotically Flat Solutions to Einstein's Equations, 1977; O'Murchada, Niall S. (Box 111)
  - Existence and Uniqueness of Solutions of the Hamiltonian Constraint of General Relativity, 1973; O'Murchada, Niall S.; York, James W., Jr. (Box 111)
  - Origin of QSO Absorption Lines, n.d.; Opher, Reuven (Box 111)
  - Three Lectures on Niels Bohr and His Times. Part III: The Atomic Nucleus, 1963; Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1904-1967 (Box 111)
  - Vacuum Energy of Gravitinos in Eleven Dimensional Supergravity, 1985; Ordonez, Carlos R.; Lütken, Carsten Andrew (Box 111)
  - Graviton Dominance in Quantum Kaluza-Klein Theory, 1985; Ordonez, Carlos R.; Rubin, Mark A. (Box 111)
  - Symmetric-Tensor Eigenspectrum of the Laplacian on n-Spheres, 1984; Ordonez, Carlos R.; Rubin, Mark A. (Box 111)
  - Analytical and Numerical Investigation of Gravitational Collapse, 1979; Pachner, Jaroslav (Box 111)
  - Problem of Gravitational Collapse: Summary of Results, [1980]; Pachner, Jaroslav (Box 111)
  - Performances of Accelerated Detectors, 1980; Padmanabhan, T. (Box 111)
  - Approximate Stress Tensors Near a Black Hole, [1982]; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 111)
  - Classical Stability of Round and Squashed Seven-Spheres in Eleven-Dimensional Supergravity, [1983]-1984; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 111)
  - Comments on John A. Wheeler, This Incredible Quantum Business, [1982]; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 111)
  - Compact Rotating Gravitational Instanton, 1978; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 111)
  - Einstein-Podolsky-Rosen Physical Reality is Completely Described by Quantum Mechanics, [1982]; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 111)
  - Fractal Set of Perpetually Bouncing Universes?, 1984; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 111)
  - Green's Functions for Gravitational Multi-Instantons, 1979; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 111)
  - How Big is the Universe Today?, 1983; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 111)
  - Inflation Does Not Explain Time Asymmetry, [1983]; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 111)
  - Information Basis for Quantum Measurements, 1982; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 111)
  - Is Gravity Quantized?, [1982]-1983; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 111)
  - Is Inflation Needed to Suppress Monopoles?, [1982]; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 111)
  - Is Our Universe an Open System?, [1982]-1983; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 111)
  - Is Quantum Gravity Deterministic and/or Time Symmetric?, 1982; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 111)
  - Measurement Basis of a Quantum Apparatus, [1982]; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 111)
  - Neutron Star Explosions?, 1982; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 111)
  - Will Entropy Decrease if the Universe Recollapses?, 1985; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson) (Box 111)
  - Two- and Three-Body Contributions to Cosmological Monopole Annihilation, 1982; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson); Dicus, Duane A.; Teplitz, Vigdor L. (Box 111)
  - Experimental Evidence for Quantum Gravity, [1980]; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson); Geilker, C. D. (Box 111)
  - Operator Ordering and the Flatness, 1985; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson); Hawking, S. W., (Stephen W.) (Box 111)
  - Thermodynamics of Black Holes in Anti-deSitter Space, 1982; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson); Hawking, S. W., (Stephen W.) (Box 111)
  - Propagation of Particles in Spacetime Foam, 1979; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson); Hawking, S. W., (Stephen W.); Pope, Christopher N. (Box 111)
  - Future of the Universe, n.d.; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson); McKee, M. Randall (Box 111)
  - Instabilities in Englert-Type Supergravity Solutions, 1984; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson); Pope, Christopher N. (Box 111)
  - New Squashed Solutions of d=11 Supergravity, 1984; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson); Pope, Christopher N. (Box 111)
  - Stability Analysis of Compactifications of d=11 Supergravity with SU(3)xSU(2)xU(1) Symmetry, 1984; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson); Pope, Christopher N. (Box 111)
  - Which Compactifications of d=11 Supergravity are Stable?, 1984; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson); Pope, Christopher N. (Box 111)
  - Evolution without Evolution: Dynamics Described by Stationary Observables, [1982]; Page, Don N., (Don Nelson); Wootters, William Kent (Box 111)
  - Einstein, Newton, and Success, 1979; Pais, Abraham, 1918-2000 (Box 112)
  - Helen Dukas, 1982; Pais, Abraham, 1918-2000 (Box 112)
  - Physics in the Making in Bohr's Copenhagen, [1990]; Pais, Abraham, 1918-2000 (Box 112)
    Originally enclosed in Series II: Pais, Abraham. 24 January [1990]
  - Reminiscences about Niels Bohr, [1963]; Pais, Abraham, 1918-2000 (Box 112)
  - Weak Interactions, 1961; Pais, Abraham, 1918-2000 (Box 112)
  - Group-Extension of the Coordinate Transformations of Supergravity, [1985]; Pandres, Dave (Box 112)
  - Unified Field Theory, 1968; Pandres, Dave (Box 112)
  - State of Degenerate Plasma at the High Densities in Neutron Stars, [1981]; Papoian, Vladimir Vladimirovich (Box 112)
  - Conformal Energy-Momentum Tensor in Riemannian Space-Time, [1972]; Parker, Leonard Emanuel, 1938- (Box 112)
  - Pair Producing Electric Fields and Pulsars, [1972]; Parker, Leonard Emanuel, 1938-; Tiomno, Jayme (Box 112)
  - [Double-Ended Statistics], [1972]; Partridge, R. B. (Box 112)
    Originally enclosed with Series I: Partridge, R. Bruce. [Received 11 September 1972]
  - Transition Space is Equivalent to Hilbert Space, [1973]; Patton, Charles M. (Box 112)
  - Maximal Observer, [1980]; Peace, Terry (Box 112)
    Originally enclosed in Series II: Miller, Gary G.
  - Observational Tests and Theoretical Problems Relating to the Conjecture that the Strength of the Electromagnetic Interaction May be Variable, 1961; 2.0 folders; Peebles, P. J. E. (Phillip James Edwin) (Box 112)
  - Complex Eigenvalues in Scattering Theory, [1959]; Peierls, Rudolf Ernst, Sir, 1907-1995 (Box 112)
  - Hypothesis about Elementary Particles, [1964]; Pendergast, Richard J. (Box 112)
  - Is the Current Situation in Physics Stranger than We Think?, [1978]; Pensinger, William L.; Paine, Douglas A. (Box 112)
  - Derivation of a Formal Atmospheric Analogue to Maxwell's Equations, 1977; Pensinger, William L.; Paine, Douglas A.; Kaplan, Michael L. (Box 112)
  - Criterion for Ellipticity and the Criterion for the Presence of Integrability Conditions, 1973; Pereira, Carlos Martin (Box 112)
  - Nonglobal Proof of the Thin-Sandwich Conjecture, 1977; Pereira, Carlos Martin (Box 112)
  - Nonglobal Proof of the Thin-Sandwich Conjecture -- Revised, 1979; Pereira, Carlos Martin (Box 112)
  - Thin-Sandwich Conjecture and a Fifth Initial Value Equation for the Gravitational Field, 1972; Pereira, Carlos Martin (Box 112)
  - Can We Undo Quantum Measurements?, [1979]; Peres, Asher, 1934- (Box 112)
  - Classic Paradoxes of Quantum Theory, 1984; Peres, Asher, 1934- (Box 112)
  - Continuous Monitoring of Quantum Systems, [1986]; Peres, Asher, 1934- (Box 112)
  - Diagonalization of the Weyl Tensor, [1978]; Peres, Asher, 1934- (Box 112)
  - Existence of Free Will as a Problem of Physics, 1986; Peres, Asher, 1934- (Box 112)
  - Internal Coordinates for a System of Fermions, 1972; Peres, Asher, 1934- (Box 112)
  - New Conserved Quantities and Test for Quantum Chaos, [1984]; Peres, Asher, 1934- (Box 112)
  - On the Nature of Physical Reality, [1984]; Peres, Asher, 1934- (Box 112)
  - Physicist's Role in Physical Laws, 1979; Peres, Asher, 1934- (Box 112)
  - Quantum Chaos and the Measurement Problem, [1986]; Peres, Asher, 1934- (Box 112)
  - Regular and Irregular Energy Spectra, 1983; Peres, Asher, 1934- (Box 112)
  - Relativistic Telemetry, [1986]; Peres, Asher, 1934- (Box 112)
  - Stability of Quantum Motion in Chaotic and Regular Systems, [1984]; Peres, Asher, 1934- (Box 112)
  - What is a State Vector?, [1983-1984]; Peres, Asher, 1934- (Box 112)
  - When is a Quantum Measurement?, 1986; Peres, Asher, 1934- (Box 112)
  - Distribution of Matrix Elements of Chaotic Systems, [1986]; Peres, Asher, 1934-; Feingold, Mario (Box 113)
  - Regular and Chaotic Propagators in Quantum Theory, [1984]; Peres, Asher, 1934-; Feingold, Mario (Box 113)
  - Calculation of Localization Length in Disordered Chains, [1981]; Peres, Asher, 1934-; Revzen, M.; Ron, Akiva (Box 113)
  - Is Quantum Theory Universally Valid?, 1980; Peres, Asher, 1934-; Zurek, Wojciech Hubert, 1951- (Box 113)
  - Niels Bohr's Philosophy -- Two Talks Given on the Danish Radio, 1963; Petersen, Aage (Box 113)
    Originally enclosed in Series I: Petersen, Aage
  - SI Units and the Fundamental Constants of Physics -- Yesterday, Today, and Tomorrow, 1981; Petley, B. W., (Brian William) (Box 113)
  - State-Transition Structures in Physics and in Computation, Petri, C. A. (Box 113)
  - Quantum Field Theory in Stationary Coordinate Systems, 1981; Pfautsch, Jonathan David (Box 113)
  - Quantized Scalar Field in the Stationary Coordinate Systems of Flat Spacetime, [1980]; Pfautsch, Jonathan David; Letaw, John R. (Box 113)
  - Stationary Coordinate Systems in Flat Spacetime, [1980]; Pfautsch, Jonathan David; Letaw, John R. (Box 113)
  - Ph. D. Theses, 1971-1972; 2.0 Volume(s) (Volume 106-107)
    Relativity Group. Under J. A. Wheeler. NSF Grant GP30799X
    - Baryon Number, Entropy, and Black Hole Physics, 1972; Bekenstein, Jacob David (Volume 106)
    - Investigations in Gravitational Collapse and the Physics of Black Holes, 1971; Christodoulou, Demetrios, 1951- (Volume 106)
    - Scalar Quantum Field Theory in a Closed Universe of Constant Curvature, 1972; Fulling, Stephen A. (Volume 106)
    - Scalar Waves and Tensor Perturbations in the Mixmaster Universe, 1972; Hu, B. L., (Bei-Lok) (Volume 107)
    - Gravitational and Electromagnetic Interactions of a Black Hole, 1972; Mashhoon, Bahram (Volume 107)
    - Global Properties of the Petrov Type D Vacuum Metrics in General Relativity, 1972; Miller, James G. (Volume 107)
    - Nonspherical Gravitational Collapse and Black Hole Uniqueness, 1972; Wald, Robert M. (Volume 107)
  - Microquakes and Macroquakes in Neutron Stars: The Restless Crab Pulsar, 1972; Pines, David, 1924-; Shaham, Jacob (Box 113)
  - Cylindrical General Relativistic Collapse, [1977]; Piran, Tsvi, 1949- (Box 113)
  - Gravitational Waves and Gravitational Collapse in Clyindrical Systems, [1977]; Piran, Tsvi, 1949- (Box 113)
  - Black Body Radiation in the Theory of Action at a Distance, 1947; Plass, Gilbert N. (Box 113)
  - On the Separation of Einsteinian Sub-Structures, [1977]; Plebanski, Jerzy (Box 113)
  - Gravity and Quantization: Doubts and Open Questions, [1961]; Plebanski, Jerzy; Bazanski, Stanislaw (Box 113)
  - General Relativity and G-Structures. I. General Theory and Algebraically Degenerate Spaces, [1977]; Plebanski, Jerzy; Boyer, Charles P. (Box 113)
  - Theory of Deformation of Structures, [1973]; Pommaret, J. F., 1945- (Box 113)
  - Kahler Manifolds and Quantum Gravity, 1981; Pope, Christopher N. (Box 113)
  - η Invariant for Charged Spinors in Taub-Nut, 1981; Pope, Christopher N. (Box 113)
  - Physical Dimensions and Covariance, [1981]; Post, Evert Jan (Box 113)
  - Spin: A Manifestation of Special Enantiomorphism, [1977]; Post, Evert Jan (Box 113)
  - Three Dimensional Periods in Electrodynamics and in Continuum Dynamics, [1977]; Post, Evert Jan (Box 113)
  - What are Time Reversal Symmetry Violations?, 1977; Post, Evert Jan (Box 113)
  - Noncomputability in Models of Physical Phenomena, n.d.; Pour-El, Marian B., (Marian Boykan), 1928-; Richards, Ian, 1936- (Box 113)
  - Transubstantiate Quantum Mechanic Phenomena, [1980]; Powell, George D. (Box 113)
  - Perfectly Oscillating Universe, 1974; Prakash, A., (Anand) (Box 114)
  - Exact Evolution of Photons in an Anisotropic Cosmology with Scattering, [1975]; Press, William H. (Box 114)
  - On the Relative Importance of Phase and Frequency Information in Pulsar Timing Measurements, [1975]; Press, William H. (Box 114)
  - Astrophysical Processes Near Black Holes, 1974; Press, William H.; Eardley, Douglas M. (Box 114)
  - Automatatheoretical Approach to Concurrency, n.d.; Priese, Lutz (Box 114)
  - Dynamical Theory of Irreversible Processes, 1977; Prigogine, I., (Ilya) (Box 114)
  - Human Values, Free Will, and the Conscious Mind, 1976; Pugh, George Edgin, 1926- (Box 114)
  - Dilational Stability of a Simple Spherical Geon, 1955; Putnam, Peter (Box 114)
  - Outline of a Functional Model of the Nervous System, 1963; Putnam, Peter (Box 114)
  - Proposed Study of the Relation of Consciousness to Physics, 1975; Putnam, Peter (Box 114)
  - Origin of Order, 1966; Putnam, Peter; Fuller, Robert W. (Box 114)
  - Einstein, Albert, 1980; Pyenson, Lewis (Box 114)
    Originally enclosed in Series II: Pyenson, Lewis. 20 January 1981
  - Is the Chemical Difference between Silver and Gold a Relativistic Effect?, [1977]; Pyykko, Pekka, 1941- (Box 114)
  - New Interpretation of the Quantum Formalism, [1978]; Qadir, Asghar (Box 114)
  - On Dirac's Large Number Hypothese, [1978]; Qadir, Asghar; Ali, S. Waqar (Box 114)
  - [Closure of Universe as Requirement for Bang to Crunch Equivalence of Observers, 1987; Qadir, Asghar; Wheeler, John Archibald, 1911-2008 (Box 114)
  - Whither Physical Objects?, 1975; Quine, W. V., (Willard Van Orman) (Box 114)
  - Relational Dynamics, A Logical Unification of Physical Theory, [1977]; Quine, W. V., (Willard Van Orman) (Box 114)
  - Hydrodynamic and Thermodynamic Phenomena in Superdense Matter: Theory and Applications, 1980; 2.0 folders; Raha, Sibaji, 1954- (Box 114)
  - Calculation of K 2 Using Regge Calculus, n.d.; Ramstad, Linda (Box 114)
  - [Unidentified manuscript], 1972; Randers, Gunnar, 1914- (Box 114)
  - Anomaly Called PSI: Recent Research and Criticism, 1987; Rao, K. Ramakrishna; Palmer, John (Box 114)
  - Ending the Faustian Bargain: Toward a Knowledge for Social Reconstruction, Raskin, Marcus G. (Box 114)
  - Application of Multi-Dimensional Descrates' Space to Relativity, Quantum Theory, and Electromagnetism, [1979]; Rauscher, Elizabeth A. (Box 114)
  - Conceptual Changes in Reality Models from New Discoveries in Physics, 1981; Rauscher, Elizabeth A. (Box 114)
  - Geometrical Constraints in Quantum Mechaincs and Cosmology, 1973; Rauscher, Elizabeth A. (Box 114)
  - Some Ideas on the Fundamental Nature of Physical Reality, [1979]; Rauscher, Elizabeth A. (Box 114)